cxholidays.com 2010-06-22

# Data Privacy and Security Policy - Cathay Pacific Holidays - Dragonair Holidays - Your holiday package travel agent

**Our Commitment to Protecting Your Privacy**

We are committed to protecting your personal and data privacy. To ensure you can make informed decisions and feel confident about supplying personally identifiable information ("Data") relating to you when using our website, this notice outlines Cathay Holidays Limited online information practices and the choices you have concerning how the Data is being collected and used.

We collect and process only information that we need to administer our business, to provide you with the highest quality service and to offer various opportunities which may be of interest to you.

This privacy statement is in compliance with the Personal Data (Privacy) Ordinance of the Hong Kong SAR.

 **Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of information about the user that a website can send to your web browser which may then store it on your computer system. With the use of cookies, we can better serve you when you return to our site. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but if you prefer, you can edit your browser options to block them in future.

**Log Files**

We may collect information regarding your IP address, browser type, domain name and access time. This information is used for our own research purposes and is stored and dealt with separately from Data. We do not link IP addresses to any personal information. In rare instances, IP addresses may be used to assist in deterring and/or preventing abusive or criminal activity on the website.

**The Way We Use Your Data**

We may use the Data you provided for one or more of the following purposes: 

To process your request on purchasing our product(s) and service(s); 

  1. To process your request to purchase our product(s) and service(s)
  2. To confirm your travel arrangements;
  3. To fulfil your request when you use our online services;
  4. To contact you regarding your enquiries;
  5. For the operations of the service providers including delivery of associated benefits and services;
  6. For our own marketing purposes, such as sending you updates on our latest offers and promotions;
  7. For our own reference and record.

We will not share the Data of users with outside party, except to the extent necessary to complete the order/request on the purchase of our product(s) and service(s), and to fulfil your request when using our online services.

We use aggregate non-identifying information about our customers to better design our website. This means that we may provide this information to third parties. However, this information will never identify any single user in particular.

We will never use or share the Data provided to us online in ways unrelated to the purposes aforementioned.

**Our Commitment to Data Security**

To maintain the accuracy of all Data, as well as to prevent unauthorized access and to ensure the correct use of the Data, we have carried out appropriate physical, electronic and managerial measures to safeguard and secure the Data we collect online. We use Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol - an industry standard for encryption over the Internet that protects Data. When you type in sensitive information such as credit card details, it will be automatically converted into code before being securely dispatched over the Internet.

The Data you provide us will be stored in a database for the length of your membership or registration validity, whichever is longer, after which it will be destroyed. The website has a firewall in place, which aim to protect Data collected from you against unauthorized or accidental access. However, complete confidentiality and security is not yet possible over the Internet, and we cannot assure complete privacy during any communication between you and us.

You should understand that personal information is disclosed at your own risk, and may be subject to unauthorized use by others. This may result in you receiving unsolicited messages from other parties. We are not responsible in any manner for direct, indirect, special or consequential damages, howsoever caused, arising from the communication of information to us.

**Your Choice**

We may occasionally send you email updates about our latest products and services, as well as special offers.

Should you prefer not to receive any email updates from us, feel free to opt out from these services by contacting us directly. Alternatively, simply replying to our email with a short note e.g. "Please do not send me email updates about your latest news and offers".

**Links to Other Sites**

This website contains links to other sites that are operated under different privacy practices. You should remain alert when you leave our site, and read the privacy statements of other websites. We have no control over Data that is submitted to these third parties.

All such websites are classed as entirely independent from this website and from Cathay Holidays Limited and its affiliates. Cathay Holidays Limited and its affiliates have no control over the contents of such other websites or their privacy policies or compliance with the law, and do not vouch for their security. You should therefore be fully aware the provision of the link does not constitute an endorsement, approval, or any form of association by or with Cathay Holidays Limited or any of its affiliates.

You should therefore remain alert when you leave our site, and read the privacy statements of other websites. We have no control over Data submitted to these third parties. You access the data on such websites at your own risk. Please note that the sites of Cathay Holidays Limited, Cathay Pacific Cargo and Asia Miles have their own separate privacy statements. We recommend you read such statements when entering these sites.

**Our Commitment to Children's Privacy**

Protecting the privacy of children is our primary concern. Therefore, we make every effort to desist from collecting Data from our website or storing this Data from those who are under 13 years of age.

**Changes to Privacy Statement**

We post new or updated statements in this section if we deem it necessary to change any part of our privacy statement. That way you are always informed of the way we collect and use the Data. If at any point we decide to use the Data you submitted under this current statement in the revised condition, you will be given the opportunity to opt out or otherwise prevent from such usage.

**Legal Disclaimer**

We may disclose Data when required by law or by court order, or as requested by other government or law enforcement authorities. It may also be revealed in good faith that disclosure is otherwise necessary or advisable including, and without limitation to protect the rights or properties of Cathay Holidays Limited. This also applies when we have reason to believe that disclosing Data is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing interference with our rights or properties, whether intentionally or otherwise, or when anyone else could be harmed by such activities.

 **This notice is written in English language and may be translated into other languages. In the event of any inconsistency between the English version and the translated version of this notice, the English version shall prevail.**
